A Guide to the Secretary of the Budget, General Administrative Records, 1918-1922;
Library of Virginia
- Special Reports 1918-1922 (Box 3, 6 and 7)
  - Report re: Fish Commission - Detroit Bureau of Governmental Research 1919 (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - Report re: Register of Land Office, No. 47 - Detroit Bureau of Governmental Research 1919 (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - Report re: State Hospital, No. 52 - Detroit Bureau of Governmental Research 1919 (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - Rifle Range 1920 (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - State Colony for Epileptics and the Feeble-Minded: Report by LeRoy Hodges 1920 (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - State Colony for Epileptics and the Feeble-Minded: Special Report, Governor's Board of Mechanical Survey 1919 (Box 3, Folder 60)
  - State Debt Commission: Miscellaneous Special Reports 1919 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - State Government, Organization of the: Special Report, Detroit Bureau of Government Research 1919 (Box 3, Folder 61)
  - Trustees Attendance Reports 1919 (Box 3, Folder 62)
  - Tuberculosis Committee 1920-1922 (Box 3, Folder 63)
  - Tuberculosis, Report of the Committee on 1920 (Box 3, Folder 64)
  - University of Virginia: Survey Report, Institute for Public Service of New York 1919 (Box 3, Folder 65)
  - Virginia College Association 1920 (Box 3, Folder 66)
  - Virginia Home & Industrial School for Girls: Survey Report, John S. Rae 1919 (Box 3, Folder 67)
  - Virginia Home and Industrial School for Girls: Special Report, Governor's Board of Mechanical Survey 1921 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Virginia Manual Labor School: Survey Report, John S. Rae 1919 (Box 3, Folder 68)
  - Virginia Military Institute: Report by LeRoy Hodges 1920 (Box 3, Folder 69)
  - Virginia Military Institute: Special Report, Governor's Board of Mechanical Survey 1919 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Virginia Normal and Industrial Institute: Special Report, Governor's Board of Mechanical Survey 1919 (Box 3, Folder 70)
  - Virginia Normal and Industrial Institute: Special Report, Governor's Board of Mechanical Survey 1919 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Virginia Polytechnic Institute: Budget Requests for 1922-1924 1921 (Box 3, Folder 71)
  - Virginia Polytechnic Institute: Report of President on Organization 1920 (Box 3, Folder 72)
  - Virginia Polytechnic Institute: Special Report, Governor's Board of Mechanical Survey 1919 (Box 3, Folder 73)
  - Virginia Polytechnic Institute: Special Report, Institute for Public Service of New York 1919 (Box 3, Folder 74)
  - Virginia School for the Deaf and Blind: Report by LeRoy Hodges 1921 (Box 3, Folder 75)
  - Virginia School for the Deaf and Blind: Special Report, Governor's Board of Mechanical Survey 1919-1921 (Box 3, Folder 76)
  - Virginia School for the Deaf and Blind: Special Report by the State Board of Charities and Corrections 1919 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Virginia State School for Colored Deaf and Blind Children, Newport News: Special Report: Governor's Board of Mechanical Survey 1919 (Box 3, Folder 77)
  - Virginia Survey Report on the Budget with Procedures - Detroit Bureau of Governmental Research 1919 (Box 3, Folder 78)
  - Virginia War History Commission: Survey Report 1919 (Box 3, Folder 79)
  - Weights and Measures: Survey Report, Institute for Public Service of New York 1919 (Box 3, Folder 80)
  - Western State Hospital: Special Report, Governor's Board of Mechanical Survey 1919-1920 (Box 3, Folder 81)
  - Western State Hospital: Report by LeRoy Hodges 1921 (Box 3, Folder 82)
  - Western State Hospital: Survey Report, Detroit Bureau of Governmental Research 1919 (Box 3, Folder 83)
- Monthly Reports 1922 (Box 3 and 6)
  Arranged alphabetically by folder title. Contains reports submitted to the secretary of the budget itemizing income and expenditures. Generally, these reports cover February and March 1922, although there are some other reports included.
  - Catawba Sanatorium -- Monthly Reports 1922 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Central State Hospital -- Monthly Reports 1922 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - College of William and Mary -- Monthly Reports 1922 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Normal School for Women at East Radford -- Monthly Reports 1922 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Normal School for Women at Fredericksburg -- Monthly Reports 1922 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Normal School for Women at Harrisonburg -- Monthly Reports 1922 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Penitentiary -- Monthly Reports 1922 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Penitentiary Farm, State -- Monthly Reports 1922 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Piedmont Sanatorium -- Monthly Reports 1922 (Box 3, Folder 84)
  - R. E. Lee Camp Soldiers' Home -- Monthly Reports 1922 (Box 3, Folder 85)
  - University of Virginia -- Monthly Reports 1922 (Box 3, Folder 86)
  - Virginia Normal and Industrial Institute -- Monthly Reports 1922 (Box 3, Folder 87)
  - Virginia School for the Deaf and Blind -- Monthly Reports 1922 (Box 3, Folder 88)
  - Virginia State School for Colored Deaf & Blind Children -- Monthly Reports 1922 (Box 6, Folder 23)
- Other Materials (Box 3 and 6)
  Arranged alphabetically by folder title. Contains various materials from the administrative papers of the secretary of the budget. Included are instructions for the preparation of the budget, information on the budget classifications, position descriptions for the state library and general office staff, and various forms collected by the office.
  - Budget, Classifications and Instructions for the Preparation of 1919 (Box 3, Folder 89)
  - Budget Classifications, Miscellaneous (Box 3, Folder 90)
  - Governor's Investigation: Proceedings of a Meeting of the General Board of Directors of the State Hospitals of Virginia 1919 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Governor's Investigation: State Board of Charities and Corrections regarding the Virginia School for the Deaf and Blind 1919 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Penitentiary Forms, Schedules, etc. (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - State Library: Position Descriptions (Box 3, Folder 91)
  - Typing, Stenographic, Correspondence, and Secretarial Work: Position Descriptions (Box 3, Folder 92)